我告诉卡尔 没有人可以爬恐龙
So I told Carl,nobody,no matter how famous their parents are...
父母再有名也一样
...is allowed to climb on the dinosaur.
可想而知，他是左耳进…
Of course,it went right in one ear....
我最喜欢他的认真了
I love how he cares so much about stuff.
要是我眯起眼睛 就能把他看成亚伦艾达（影星）
If I squint,I can pretend he's Alan Alda.
拜托，又在讲恐龙的事
Oh,good. Another dinosaur story.
这些事什么时候才会绝种？
When are those gonna become extinct?
如果我是一个会飞 还会隐形的超级英雄
If I was a superhero who could fly and be invisible...
那就太棒了
... that would be the best.
瑞秋到底看上他哪一点？
What does Rachel see in this guy?
我爱瑞秋
I love Rachel.
真希望她是我的老婆
I wish she was my wife.
谁在唱歌？
Who's singing?
本集播出：“赛车床”
The One With the Race Car Bed
你们小时候扮演电视剧《欢乐时光》里的角色时
When you guys were kids and you played Happy Days...
都扮成什么？我都当里奇
...who were you? I was Richie.
我都当乔安妮（是兄妹，并且特别吵）
I was always Joanie.
请问“蛋洗盖勒家” 是你们邻居的口号吗？
Question: Was "Egg the Gellers!" the war cry of your neighborhood?
“床垫大王特价实施中”
是床垫大王
It's the Mattress King!
赶快转台
Change the channel!
等一下，我想看 等我跟他离了婚
Wait! I want to see this! After I divorce him...
有一半的王国将属于我
...half of that kingdom is gonna be mine!
床垫卖场愁云惨怖
Despair fills the mattress showroom.
我的王国突然失去皇后
My Kingdom is suddenly without a Queen.
我是如此沮丧
I'm so depressed...
我决定将价格
...I'm going to slash...
砍到最低！
...my prices!
各位请看
Check it out!
加利福尼亚之王只要599
599 for a California king!
有枕垫的皇后床垫只要499
499 for a pillow-top queen set!
我的价格非常保守
I'm going medieval on prices!
那个小人
What a wank!
他居然拿我们的离婚来促销
I cannot believe he's using our divorce to sell mattresses!
有枕垫的床垫只要499 谁管你离不离婚？
I know. At $499 for a pillow-top queen,who cares about the divorce?
那些床垫自己都能卖
Those babies will sell themselves!
还有，我很为你吃惊
And I'm appalled for you,by the way.
卖场最近，价格最低 我是床垫之王
I'm close! I'm cheap! I'm the King!
他的下体是填充的，对吗
He stuffs that codpiece, right?
是的 （不）
Oh, yeah.No
好了，拿去
Okay, here you go.
你知道吗，我不要顶上飘着肉桂的
You know what?l asked for no cinnamon on top.
好的，爸爸，我们明晚见 好，再见
Okay,Daddy. We'll see you tomorrow night. Okay,bye-bye.
我们？
"We"?
…明晚要跟我爸吃饭 没问题吧？
are having dinner with my Dad tomorrow night. I hope that's okay.
糟糕，明天不方便
Oh,shoot! Tomorrow's not good.
我应该会从帝国大厦掉下来
I'm supposed to fall off the Empire State Building...
跌到没有座的脚踏车上 所以…
...and land on a bicycle with no seat,so....
我爸并不讨厌你
My father doesn't hate you.
拜托，他管我叫“油头”
Please. He refers to me as "Wet-Head."
他都叫别人的绰号
Honey,he calls everybody by a nickname.
好，就一顿饭 一个晚上，为了我
I know. Just one dinner. One night. For me. Please?
我只是想让他像我一样爱你
I just want him to love you like I do.
好吧，也许不能像我一样
All right. Well,not exactly like I do.
不过如果你肯来
But if you do come to dinner...
我就穿那件黑色性感内衣 好好爱你
...I'll love you like I do in that black thing that you like.
我去
I'll go.
好吧
Fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗨 甘瑟
Hi,Gunther.
等着瞧
Yeah. We'll see.
大家好
Hey,you guys!
你们猜怎样？
Guess what.
我有演出（法语）了
-I got a gig! -Great!
所以我当不成演员 我不会说“gig”
That's why I can never be an actor. I can't say "gig."
我不会说“croissant”（法语“面包”） 天哪！
I can't say "croissant." Oh,my God!
是什么角色？ 不是角色
-What's the part? -It's not a part.
我要去学习扩展学校 教“连续剧演技”
I'm teaching Acting for Soap Operas at the Learning Extension.
很棒啊
Come on! That's great!
我可以借此机会
It's my chance to give something back...
回馈演艺界
...to the acting community.
你应该不可以跟学生上床
You're probably not allowed to sleep with your students.
我知道
I know.
“床垫大王”
我不晓得 光是来这里，感觉就很怪
I don't know,Monica. It feels funny just being here.
跟珍妮丝的前夫买床铺
If you buy a bed from Janice's ex-husband...
就像在背叛钱德
...it's like betraying Chandler.
这种价格耶
Not at these prices!
这辆车在英国应该在店的另一边（英国车的驾驶座在右边）
You know,in England this car would be on the other side of the store.
菲比，过来
Come here.
这就是我的新床铺
This is my new bed!
你一定要感受一下
You gotta feel this bad boy!
莫妮卡，我还是觉得怪怪的
Monica,it still feels so weird,you know?
钱德是你的朋友
Chandler's your friend.
我的天哪
Oh,my God!
买吧，朋友可以再交
All right,take this bed. You can make other friends.
“乔瑟夫崔比亚尼”
晚安
Good evening.
我是崔比亚尼老师
I am Mr. Tribbiani.
我将教大家“连续剧演技”
And I will be teaching Acting for Soap Operas.
不幸的是，今晚是我的唯一的一次课
Unfortunately, tonight will be my only class...
因为一种罕见的血液病毒，我只剩两星期的寿命了
...because due to a rare blood disease l only have two weeks to live.
那么我们能拿回我们的学费吗
So do we get our deposit back?
这只是一个表演肥皂剧的例子
That was supposed to be an example of acting for soap operas.
那么为什么你只有今晚上课呢
Then why are you only teaching tonight?
我不是，看，这就是我们没有直接上课的原因了，明白了吗
l'm not. Look, why don't we get straight to the lesson, okay?
现在…
Now...
在我参与“我们的日子” 演出雷莫瑞医生的第一天
...on my first day as Dr. Drake Ramoray on Days Of Our Lives...
我学到演连续剧时 很重要的一点
... I learned one of the most important things in soap opera acting...
就是回应
...is reacting.
意思不是“回去反应”
This does not mean acting again.
而是你没有台词 但可以听别人讲
It means you don't have a line,but someone else just did.
就像这样
And it goes something like this.
谢了
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
还有，先说明一点 如果想演连续剧
By the way,before I forget. To work in soap operas...
有些同学得让自己变漂亮
...some of you will have to become more attractive.
好，继续往下讲
All right,moving right along....
昨晚课上得怎样？ 很棒，我可以说…
-How was teaching last night? -Great! You get to say stuff like...
打铃并不代表下课 我说下课才能下课
... "Hey,the bell doesn't dismiss you. I dismiss you."
真好
Oh,nice.
还有，我要去肥皂剧“我的孩子们”试镜
Oh,and I got an audition for All My Children!
是一个很棒的角色
It's this great part.
拳击手尼克
This boxer named Nick.
我超适合的，他跟我一模一样
And I'm so,so right for it. He's just like me.
除了他是拳击手之外
Except that he's a boxer...
还有一个坏蛋双胞胎兄弟
...and has an evil twin.
听我说，听我说，床垫大王送货来了
Hear ye,hear ye! Delivery from the Mattress King!
盖勒小姐吗？
You Miss Geller?
请签收
Sign here.
我有中间的名字吗？
Do I have a middle name?
好吧，莫妮卡“费露拉”…
All right. Monica "Felula"...
盖勒
...Geller.
抬到那个房间
It's that bedroom there.
莫妮卡跟床垫大王买床？
Monica bought a bed from the Mattress King?
求求你，不要告诉钱德
Please,please,please don't say anything to Chandler.
你要我骗他？ 有问题吗？-没有
-You want me to lie to him? -ls that a problem?-No
拳击手尼克，露两手来瞧瞧
Oh,hey,"Nick the boxer." Let's see what you got!
拳头举起来
All right,put them up.
你蛮有架势的嘛
Hey,you're pretty good at this.
我非学不可 我住在基督教青年会时
I had to learn. I was staying at the "Y"...
有些男生不像基督徒
...and some of the young men weren't acting Christian enough.
别闹了
Hey,now!
我流血了，天呐
And I'm bleeding. Okay,great.
我是素食者耶
Wow! And I'm a vegetarian!
对不起，来冰敷吧
I'm sorry. We'll put some ice on it.
把头仰起来 好
Put your head back.
我看不到 我来牵你
-I can't see. -I have you.
天哪
Oh,God!
盖勒小姐，要抬进哪个房间？
Which bedroom do you want it in,Ms. Geller?
靠窗有洁癖的那一间
It's the compulsively neat one by the window.
知道了
Gotcha.
爸爸
Hi,Daddy!
位子被排在这里？
This is where they put us?
怎么？厨房放不下桌子了吗？
What? There was no table in the kitchen?
乖女儿 记得罗斯吧
-Hello,baby. -You remember Ross.
格林医生，又见面了
Nice to see you again,Dr. Greene.
所以…
So!
图书馆还好吗？ 是博物馆
-How's the library? -Museum.
那图书馆呢？ 没有图书馆
-What happened to the library? -There never was a library.
是有图书馆，只不过…
I mean,there are libraries. It's just...
我没在图书馆做过事
...that I've never worked at one.
知道这里的名菜是什么？ 龙虾
You know what's really good here? The lobster.
我直接点三份吧 如果你很饿的话
-Shall I just order three? -lf you're really hungry.
那是在开玩笑
It was a joke. I made a joke.
其实罗斯对龙虾过敏
Actually,Daddy,Ross is allergic to lobster.
谁会对龙虾过敏？ 我猜是图书馆员
Who's allergic to lobster? I guess someone that works in a library.
不是… 我知道，是博物馆
-It's -I know. It's a museum!
只有你可以开玩笑吗？ 至少我的很好笑
You're the only who can make a joke? At least mine was funny.
服务生
Waiter.
两份龙虾，一份菜单
We will have two lobsters and a menu.
格林医生，你的船好吗？
So,Dr. Greene,how's the old boat?
生锈了，你知道生锈会怎样？
They found rust. Do you know what rust does to a boat?
让船看起来很古典？
Gives it a nice antique-y look?
锈是船的癌症，罗斯
Rust is boat cancer,Ross.
我真遗憾
Wow,I'm sorry.
我小时候就这样 失去了一辆脚踏车
When I was a kid,I lost a bike to that.
失陪一下
Excuse me for a moment.
我想在离开之前 去问候莱文家的人
I want to say good night to the Levines before we go.
亲爱的，别这样，没那么糟
Honey,stop. It's not that bad.
你爸一定算错了 他只给了4%的小费
Your dad must have added wrong. He only tipped 4%.
是啊，爸就是这样
Yeah. That's Daddy.
爸就是这样？ 你不困扰吗？你是服务生耶
"That's Daddy"? Doesn't it bother you? You're a waitress.
我的确很困扰
Yes,it bothers me.
如果他常来 我会在他的咖啡里加胡椒
If he was a regular at the coffee house,I'd be serving him sneezers.
所以呢？ 所以…
-So? -So,Ross...
我跟他说过几千遍了 他就是不改
... I've bugged him about this a million times. He won't change.
你真的会在咖啡里加胡椒？
Do you really serve people sneezers?
不会
Well,I don't.
孩子们，可以走了吗？
All right,kids. Ready?
格林医生，再次谢谢你
Thanks again,Dr. Greene.
等一下，我忘了拿收据
Wait,I think I forgot my receipt.
不要拿了 为什么？
-You don't need that. -Why not?
碳粉很脏 会沾到手指，引发…
The carbon. It's messy. I mean,gets on your fingers and causes...
夜盲症
... night blindness.
这是什么？
What is this?
谁放了20元？
Who put a 20 down here?
是我
Oh,yeah,that would be me.
我有一个毛病
I have a problem.
我给的小费太高了
I tip way too much. Way too much.
这是一种病 没错
-It's a sickness,really. -Yeah,it is.
我们得想个办法 很抱歉
-We have to do something about that. -Excuse me.
你觉得我很小器？
You think I'm cheap?
他没有那个意思，真的
He didn't mean anything by that. He really didn't.
我做的事都没有意义，真的
Nothing I do means anything. Really.
真好啊，我花200元请客
This is nice. I pay $200 for dinner.
你只放了20元 就成了大人物
You put down $20 and you come out looking like Mr. Big Shot.
你那么想当大人物？
You really want to be Mr. Big Shot? Here.
这样吧，钱都由你出，大人物，好吗
I'll tell you what. You pay the whole bill,Mr. Big Shot. All right?
“大人物”总比“油头”好
Well,"Mr. Big Shot" is better than "Wet-Head."
现在教你们几个诀窍
Okay,some tricks of the trade.
我演戏一向哭不出来
Now,I've never been able to cry as an actor...
所以要是我得哭
...so if I have to cry...
我就把口袋挖一个洞
... I cut a hole in my pocket...
放一把镊子在里面
...take a pair of tweezers...
然后开始拔毛
...and just start pulling.
如果我想表现…
Or let's say I want to convey...
刚做了坏事的感觉
...that I've just done something evil.
就秀出基本的 “我爱眉毛上的鱼钩”的表情
That would be your basic I've-got-a- fish-hook-in-my-eyebrow-and-l-like-it.
要是我听到一个坏消息
Let's say I've just gotten bad news.
只要心算232 除以13就行了
Well,all I do there is try and divide 232 by 13.
就是这样
And that's how it's done.
今晚的课上得很愉快
Great soap opera acting tonight,everybody.
下课
Class dismissed.
崔比老师
Hey,Mr. Trib.
你猜怎样？我要去试镜了
Guess what? I got an audition!
我的学生要试镜了，我好骄傲
One of my students got an audition. I'm so proud!
能不能请您指导我？
I was wondering if you'd coach me for it.
当然可以，是什么角色？
You bet! What's the part?
那个角色很棒
Oh,it's great!
是“我的孩子们”里的 拳击手尼克
It's a role on All My Children. Nick the boxer.
你必须这么做吗？你就不能不管吗
You had to do it.You couldn't leave it alone.
才4%，就算菜里有虫 我给得都比较多
Four percent,okay? I tip more than that when there's a bug in my food.
今晚你们好不容易处得不错
Tonight was about the two of you getting along.
快去找我的按摩治疗师好吗？
Would you just see my chiropractor already?
是啊，我要去见一个来自小商场医科学校的治疗师
I'm gonna go to a doctor who went to medical school in a mini-mall.
菲比，你在干什么？
Hey,Pheebs. What are you doing?
我快吓死了
I'm freaking out!
莫妮卡交待我办一件事 她不该这么做
Monica trusted me with something and she shouldn't have!
我搬走一阵子了 所以我得问你
I haven't lived here in a while,so I have to ask you.
莫妮卡睡觉时还是会开灯吗？
Does Monica still turn the lights on in her room?
我死定了
I am so dead!
好吧，这是底线
Look,here's the bottom line.
赶紧补救还来得及
This is fixable if we act fast,okay?
我找他明天来吃早午餐 你可以示好
I'll invite him to brunch tomorrow,and you can make nice.
我示好过了，没有用
Honey,I have tried to make nice. It doesn't work.
我知道我爸很难相处
Look,I realize my father is difficult.
所以你一定要比他宽容
But that's why you have got to be the bigger man here.
我可以比他宽容 我可以超级宽容
Sweetie,I could be the bigger man. I could be the biggest man.
就算我当一个巨人 事情也不会改变
I could be a huge,giant man,and it still wouldn't make a difference.
除非我可以把你爸拎起来说 喜欢我吧，小医生！
Except I could pick your father up and say,"Like me! Like me,tiny doctor!"
你就不能再试一次吗？ 就当是为了我
Can't you just try it one more time? For me? For me?
吃早午餐也不能解决什么
One brunch is not gonna solve anything.
面对现实吧，我们合不来
Face it. We're never gonna get along.
你们非合得来不可
Well,you are just going to have to.
我已经有一对 无法共处一室的父母
I've already got a mother and father who cannot stay in the same room.
我不想再多你一个
I don't want to have a separate room for you too!
我去买焙果
I'll get the bagels.
这是什么？
What's this?
很酷吧？
Isn't it cool?
这不是我订的床
This is not the bed I ordered.
我知道 你一定是赢了什么比赛
I know! You must have won a contest or something.
这辆车为什么在我的房里？
Why is this car in my bedroom?
对不起，我没有注意
I'm sorry. I wasn't looking...
他们不肯接受退货 因为你签收了
...and the store won't take it back,because you signed for it.
我什么时候签收了？ 当我是你的时候
-When did I sign for it? -When I was you.
都是乔伊不好，他没护住鼻子
It's all Joey's fault,because he left his nose open!
你今天吃了巧克力方饼吗？
Did you make brownies today?
有人在吗？
IKnock,knock!
快脱衣服，他就不会注意到床
Quick! Take off your dress. He won't notice the bed.
我要去吃寿司，有人要…
I'm going for sushi. Does anybody want?
有人忘了驶出高速公路吗？
Somebody missed the off-ramp!
这是莫妮卡的床，怎样？
It's Monica's bed. What?
这是一辆赛车
It's a racecar!
莫妮卡的床一直都是这张 你现在才发现？
This has always been Monica's bed. You just noticed?
你还真自我中心
How self-involved are you?
如果这不是新床 床垫上为什么有胶膜？
If this bed isn't new,then how come there's plastic on the mattress?
我有时候会做恶梦
Sometimes I have bad dreams.
听着…
Look...
我刚看到我的死党 脑浆溅在画布上
... I just saw my best friend's brain smeared across the canvas.
我不要跟他一样
It's not gonna be me.
我不要
Not me.
太精彩了
That was good.
太…
That was
用镊子了吗？ 没有
Tweezers?
演得非常好 谢谢
-That was really good. -Thanks.
您有什么建议吗？
Any suggestions?
你叫他演成拳击手同性恋？
You told him to play the boxer gay?
我说的应该是…
I might have said...
“越明显越好”
... "super-gay."
乔伊，上次一个演员做了这样的坏事，导致了一个总统死了
Joey, the last time an actor did something this bad, a president died.
林肯 布斯（行刺林肯的演员）
Lincoln. Booth.
隧道出问题了吗？（乔伊以为是林肯轿车）
Something happened at the tunnel?
你是他的老师，怎么能这样？
You're this guy's teacher. How could you do this?
因为他演得太好了
Because the guy's so good.
我真的很想拿到这个角色
And I really,really want this part.
要是你真的很想，那就没关系
Well,if you really,really want it,then it's okay.
爸爸 宝贝
-Hi,Daddy. -Baby.
罗斯 格林医生，你好吗？
Dr. Greene,how are you?
谢谢你昨晚请客
Thanks for dinner last night.
谢谢你给我上了宝贵的一课
Thank you for teaching me a valuable lesson.
好帅的发型 你是游泳来的吗？
Nice hair. What did you do,swim here?
够了，我受不了了
That's it. I can't take it anymore.
怎么了？他喜欢你的发型 想知道你是怎么来的
What? He likes your hair and just wants to know how you got here.
没有用的，我要走了 什么？
-It's hopeless. I'm just gonna go. -What?
对不起，我实在… 罗斯？
-I'm sorry. It's just -Ross?
你的脖子怎么了？
What's with the neck?
他的脖子不舒服 我一直叫他去找我的按摩师
I keep telling him to go to my chiropractor.
你还在找他？
You still going to him?
他连乡下的医学院都考不上
He couldn't get into med school in lxtapa!
谢谢，我一直这么说
Thank you. That's what I keep saying.
很抱歉 巴比医生是个很好的医生
Excuse me,Dr. Bobby happens to be an excellent doctor.
等一下，他叫巴比医生？
Wait a minute. His name is Dr. Bobby?
那是他的姓 和他的名字
-That's his last name. -And his first name.
他叫巴比巴比？
He's Bobby Bobby?
是劳勃巴比
It's Robert Bobby.
而且很抱歉，他把我医好了
And excuse me. He helps me.
拜托！你问她 你哪里有毛病？
-Please. Ask her how? -What do you need help for?
我歪一边，有一条腿比较短
My alignment. One leg's shorter than the other.
拜托！ 跟她辩论一下
-Oh,my God. -Argue with that.
本来就是，我的右腿短了两英寸
My right leg is two inches shorter!
拜托，你只是没站直
Come on,you're just tilting!
她的腿好得很 我知道
-Her legs are fine. -I know that.
那你为什么让她去？ 让她去？
-So why do you let her go to him? -"Let her"?
她连承租保险的事都不听我的
She doesn't listen to me about renter's insurance,either.
慢着，你没有承租保险？
Wait a minute. You don't have renter's insurance?
要是遭小偷 你要用长短脚追吗？
How you gonna run after a thief,with one leg shorter than the other?
你要喝果汁吗？ 我喜欢果汁
-Would you like some juice? -I'd love some juice.
真顺利，你看到我们了吗？
This is going so well! Did you see us? Did you see?
看到了，我就站在旁边
Yeah,honey. I was standing right there.
你怎么不提我那颗痣的事？
Why don't you tell him about my mole?
好主意
Excellent!
有一天，在你们的事业生涯里
There will come a time in each of your careers...
你们会有机会毁掉 另一个连续剧演员
...when you'll have a chance to screw over another soap opera actor.
前不久，我就有这样的机会
I had such an opportunity in the recent present.
很惭愧的是…
And I'm ashamed to say...
我也做了
...that I took it.
我建议另一位演员把一个角色
I advised a fellow actor to play a role...
演成同性恋
... homosexually.
我们都去应征那个角色
We both auditioned for the part...
结果是…
...and as it turned out...
他们…
...they....
他们喜欢同性恋的演法 选了他
They liked the stupid "gay" thing and cast him.
现在，
And now...
他拿到两年的合约…
... he's got a two-year contract...
要和苏珊鲁奇（肥皂剧天后）合作
...opposite Susan Lucci...
日间电视剧的第一女王
...the first lady of daytime television.
而我呢？
And me?
我困在这里教别人演戏
Me,I'm stuck here teaching a bunch of people...
大多数丑到根本上不了电视
... most of whom are too ugly to even be on TV.
对不起…
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
有什么需要吗？ 有，你好
-May I help you? -Yes,hi.
我就是被硬塞一张赛车床的人
I'm the lady who got stuck with the racecar bed.
我跟你说过了，我无能为力
Look,it's like I told you. There's nothing I can do.
你签收了 “莫妮卡费露拉盖勒”
You signed for it. "Monica Felula Geller."
我们要见床垫大王
All right,we wanna see the King.
没有人可以见大王
Nobody sees the King.
好，那我要找他说话
Okay. I'm talking to the King.
你不能到后面去
Hey,you can't go back there!
我…的…天！
Oh,my God.
小姐，小心一点
Hey,watch it,lady!
美女喔
Hey,good-looking.
好，我走
All right,I'll leave.
我的床好无聊
My bed's so boring.